# KENT TUNEBERG

Rockford, IL

**Phone**: (815)-621-5184 | **Email**: ktunebe@gmail.com **LinkedIn**: https://www.linkedin.com/in/kent-tuneberg-59a191320

**Portfolio**: https://github.com/ktunebe

#### **SUMMARY**

Driven and well-rounded full stack web developer with a web development certificate in progress from The University of Wisconsin. Experience in web design utilizing proficiencies in both front-end and back-end programming, with the ability to design, build and maintain web applications. Strong abilities in problem solving and communication with a propensity for on-the-fly critical thinking and adjustment to the changing needs of a team or project.

#### TECHNICAL SKILLS

Softwares/Platforms: Express.js, React.js, Node.js, testing, computer science, database theory,

MongoDB, SQL, Git, BootstrapCSS, TailwindCSS **Software Languages:** HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Python

#### **PROJECTS**

### **Dungeons and Dragonites**

GitHub Repo: https://github.com/ktunebe/dungeons\_and\_dragonites Deployed Application: https://ktunebe.github.io/dungeons\_and\_dragonites

- A dungeon crawl game using PokeAPI and D&D 5e API. Use a random Pokémon to fight an endless barrage of D&D monsters.
- Roles: Front end designer for battle page, including animations and modal pop-ups. Dice roll and battle logic Javascript.
- HTML, TailwindCSS, Javascript, API fetch requests

#### HoliDb

GitHub Repo: https://github.com/ktunebe/holiDB Deployed Application: https://holidb.onrender.com

- A movie search database using the TMDB node package to find movies, tag them by holiday, or even create your own holiday. This uses PostgreSQL and Sequelize to keep track of users, movies and holidays.
- Roles: Front end design and styling, search functionality, Handlebars helper functions...
- HTML, TailwindCSS, Javascript, API fetch requests, Express.js, Node.js, Handlebars, PostgreSQL

## Console.blog()

GitHub Repo: https://github.com/ktunebe/magnificent-virtual-compositions-tech-blog Deployed Application: https://mvc-tech-blog-65rn.onrender.com

- A blog allowing users to add posts and comment on others using a Model-View-Controller Framework and a PostgreSQL database.
- Role: Start to finish creation, development and deployment
- HTML, TailwindCSS, Javascript, Express.js, Node.js, PostgreSQL, Sequelize, Handlebars

#### CAREER EXPERIENCE

# **General Dentist Dr. Perry K. Tuneberg and Associates**

2015-2023 Rockford, IL

Practiced as a general dentist, which involved diagnosis and treatment of dental conditions, caring for and educating patients, and a strong leadership role in a diverse team environment. Also gained proficiencies in working with dental software and digital radiography.

- Oversaw day-to-day responsibilities of a team of about 25 employees while at times seeing 25-30 patients per day.
- Well-respected member of the dental community and consistent involvement in charitable events and donated dental service programs.
- Winnebago County Dental Society Board Member 2019-2022, including President from 2021-2022

#### **EDUCATION**

Full Stack Web Development Certificate: University of Wisconsin, Madison, WI (Anticipated completion August 2024)

A 24 week intensive program focused on gaining skills in full stack web development. The course covers HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Express.js, React.js, Node.js, Python, testing, computer science, database theory, MongoDB, SQL, Git, and other modern web skills and technologies.

**Doctorate in Dental Medicine (DMD):** Southern Illinois University School of Dental Medicine 2011 - 2015

Obtained a DMD degree and a license to practice dentistry.

**Bachelor of Science:** Augustana College, Rock Island, IL 2007 - 2011

Majored in Biology with a minor in Biochemistry.